so good afternoon
everyone and now it's finally time for
our next
question question number four of today
so in total now it will be our
uh it will be our 34th question out of
75 questions
so now let's uh quickly begin with our
question
so as a responsible citizen
you always wear helmets while riding
however you also love listening to
fm radio you will a
wear helmet and use ear plugs inside
b not via helmet till
your favorite show uh till your favorite
show is on
c will not view earplugs
till you reach destination or
d you will buy smaller earphones
so so this was our question
and i hope all of you will participate
in this quiz contest and uh
all of you will answer this because you
know just by this simple step
of answering this question we uh we have
a lot of gains you know
uh we can learn a lot we can change
ourselves we can make
our indian roads safer you know first of
all is that we will get awareness
you know by answering this simple
question
we will know that uh that as a
responsible citizen
what should be our behavior on the roads
the second is that we can save many
lives of those people
who are dying because of road crashes
every day
uh you know millions of us drive on
indian roads
every day but 415 people never come back
home which is really sad
and to lessen that number to make sure
that
lesser people die on indian roads
uh you know we can start with this
simple step
uh first by awareness and then by
uh you know making sure that we uh we
as a citizen start following all these
traffic rules all these road safety
rules
because they are for our own
safety you know first of all uh we will
get unless the second thing is that we
can save
people's life and then what else can
happen
if uh if you answer correct if you
give the correct answer then you can win
some
exciting prizes either bike safety kit
for you and your family
or a car safety kit so you know just
think about that
how nice it is you know
just by this simple step of answering a
small
question uh you know we can do so many
things we can get awareness we will get
aware that what
our behavior should be there on roads
and
we can save lives of people and also we
can win some prizes also so it's
uh you know really amazing that by this
simple step of answering this question
uh we can we can you know do
a lot of things and answering this
question doesn't take a lot of time also
so i will just once again repeat the
question
so as a responsible citizen
you always be a helmet while writing
however you also love listening to fm
radio
you will a via helmet and use
earplugs inside b
not via helmet till your favorite show
is on
c will not be your earplugs till you
reach your destination
d by smaller earphones
so i will just once again repeat this in
hindi also
[Music]
will not be an ear plugs till you reach
your destination
[Music]
earphones
so you know by this simple step as we
discussed
we can do a lot and it is also really
easy and really simple to answer
you know either you can answer this with
the help of link in the description or
you can also answer this from our
youtube page
or from our facebook page also so it is
really easy
and this question it will be it will be
valid for only two hours
uh and then a next question will come so
like this
every day five questions will come uh
every two hours
each each of those questions will be
valid
for two hours only so uh you know by
this simple step we all can
start with it we can start by first
uh by first answering this question
uh you know as we just discussed
awareness
simple to answer with the help of the
link in the description you can answer
or from the youtube pages from the
facebook page also you can answer
so it is really simple and easy method
which
does not
[Music]
road safety rules and follow karnataki
uh you know children but for our own
lives
you know to make sure that everyone is
we all can start with this simple step
you know you can become a part of it by
simply answering this question
uh so i will request all of you to
become a part of this
and participate in this question as well
as
the other questions which will be coming
as well so i will once again repeat this
question
so as a responsible citizen
you always be your helmet while riding
however you also love listening to fm
radio
you will so you know you are a
responsible citizen
and you always be a helmet why you are
on
a on a two-wheeler but you also like
listening to you also like listening to
fm radio
so in this situation what will you do
when you know you have to be a helmet
also and you have also
uh want to listen to the fm radio so in
this situation
what will you do a you will
via helmet and use ear plugs inside
b uh you will not be a helmet
till your favorite show is on
or see uh will not be your earplugs
till you reach your destination or d
by smaller earphones so
i will just once again repeat this in
hindi also s
you also want to listen to the fm radio
so what will you do a via
helmet and use earplugs inside up helmet
understanding
smaller earphones so uh you know it's
really simple
and all of you can answer this uh
as well as the other questions also you
know please become a part of this
and uh and also you know uh you can also
tell
about this to other people as well you
can tell
uh your family you can also tell your
friends about this
keep will be is a joint
[Music]
you know so we all can do this
uh together and it's also really simple
you know hard to contain
you know every day there will be five
questions and
ah and they will be in a gap of two
hours
so jessica be three o'clock fourth
questionnaire
basically
with that link in the description or
uh or from our facebook page or from our
youtube page also and uh about the
results
uh the results uh every day at 10 pm
we have a show called bluntly speaking
the results
as well as the answers they will be
uh they will be told in that show
results or answers
and uh the results uh you can also see
the results on our web page also
so uh so you know please be a part of
this
you know so
now i will just once again repeat this
question
so as a responsible citizen you
always wear helmet while riding
however you also love listening to fm
radio
you will a wear helmets
and use ear plugs inside b
not v helmet till your favorite show is
on
c will not be your earplugs
till you reach your destination or d
by smaller earphones
you know so your body simply uh you know
up
description say youtube uh youtube page
say your facebook page
uh you know results will be announced
[Music]
up there so thank you so much everyone
and uh you know please be a part of this
and
you know start following all these
traffic rules
uh because we all know they are for our
own safety
so thank you so much everyone